<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Welcome to Nantong</string>
    <string name="nihao">Nantong (Chinese: 南通) is a prefecture-level city in Jiangsu province, China. Located on the northern bank of the Yangtze River, near the river mouth. Nantong is a vital river port bordering Yancheng to the north, Taizhou to the west, Suzhou and Shanghai to the south across the river, and the East China Sea to the east. Its current population is 7,282,835 at the 2010 census, 1,994,708 of whom live in the built-up area made up of three urban districts.</string>
    <string name="food1"> Asiatic Hard Clam (Meretrix Linnaeus or Wenha 文蛤): Asiatic Hard Clams are a plentiful product of the South Yellow Sea. They are one of the foremost delicacies in the world and were once sent to the emperor’s palace as a tribute.  The Asiatic hard clam can be cooked a number of ways including quick frying, simmering, and baking. Famous dishes include the Iron Plate Asiatic Hard Clam and Jin Qian Asiatic Hard Clam Cake.</string>
    <string name="food2">Wenfeng Double Bamboo (Wenfeng Shuang Zhu文峰双竹): Wenfeng Double Bamboo is a famous dish from Wenfeng Restaurant. The main ingredients are bamboo razor clams and bamboo shoots, which are quick fried to produce a delicious dish.</string>
    <string name="river">Haohe River is an open scenic area with the city as its center. Haohe River is the old city moat and flows around the city with a water surface area of 700,000 square meters. The river is known as the emerald necklace of the city. There are so many scenic spots along its course that Nantong looks like a garden full of trees and flowers. Tian Ning Temple’s Guangxiao Pagoda is located at the northern head of the river. Guangxiao Pagoda is said to predate Nantong city (Old Tong Zhou). In the southeastern area is the Nantong Museum, which was built by Zhang Jian. It is the earliest museum founded by the Chinese people themselves and it is now one of the National Key Cultural Relics Protection Units. It’s also regarded as a precious pearl on the emerald necklace by locals and tourists alike. San Yuan Bridge and Wenfeng Pagoda are other scenic spots in the area. The beautiful scenery and clean environment attracts many tourists. The southwestern area is the main scenic area and was built on the old Five Park site.</string>
    <string name="hill1">Langshan Scenic Area is located in the southern suburbs of Nantong. It’s a famous natural reserve with a number of attractive mountains including Lang Shan, Ma’an Shan, Huangni Shan, Jian Shan, and Jun Shan. The Yangtze River borders the area to the south.</string>
    <string name="hill2">Wolf Hill (Lang Shan) is in the middle of the 5 hills and has an altitude of 106.94 meters, making it the highest among them. As you enter Langshan, you will see Farutang which was the site of Da Xiong Bao Palace. Besides this there is Jin Gang Palace, Langshan Capeway, Water Paradise, and Jianzhen Memorial Pagoda. Meilin Spring Dawn, perched on the western slope of Ma’an Hill, is a building complex in the Jiang Nan Garden style.</string>
</resources>
